God is still saying something.
On the 29th of December 2013, Prophet TB Joshua prophesied a coming challenge in the Aviation industry,
That would negatively affect both passengers & airlines.
Let's Listen to him.
Those of us that are into the business of airline.
Or you call it aeroplanes, or flying or whatever.
You will be at the airport for two or three days you might not get a flight to get to where you are going.
Because the demand will be more than supply.
There will be shortage of flying; airline, airplane, shortage.
The little that is on the ground will be destroyed, damaged
But the new one, nobody to purchase them.
It will be so difficult; the business will not be as usual.
Today you get to the airport and you are waiting for a flight
They say, "No, the flight is not going".
It is still moderate
Next year, it will be more serious
And that will make the flight ticket multiply by two - the one you are having now.
Because the demand is more than what? (supply) More than supply.
Most especially in Africa: it will affect Africa so much. Africa continent most especially.
It will now become a transport on the ground.
You know when you are waiting at the bus stop,
It always takes time to get transport from one station to another.
And if you now get it, you will have to fight to enter; so also the kind of picture I'm seeing happen.
The little we have is not well managed.
And it is too old to even manage.
I am talking about the African Continent,
Too old to manage.
And 50 percent of this will be grounded
And the remaining 50 percent, there will not be enough money to manage them.
So, those of us that fly from one country to another, you should think twice -
What will happen next
If your business is about flying from one country to another,
I think there will be a challenge
Step into the future!
Be the first to know
Find out what God has to say concerning,
Your Situation.
Your Country.
And the World.
God is still saying something
A compilation of prophecies concerning individuals, nations and the world at large -
Together with their confirmations.
I am seeing flame what is the meaning of that?
In every situation God has something to say.
Find out what God has to say.
God is still saying something.